onlyblowjob.com 2019-03-08

# Privacy Policy

By logging on and using the Site, you agree to and accept our privacy policy. We understand that sharing your personal information with us over the internet requires trust. We value your trust very highly, and pledge to you that we will protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us through our websites. This includes your name, address, phone number, email address, and any other personal information that can be linked to you. We will collect and use information about your preferences and browsing habits to help personalize your experience on the website. In case you do not agree with this, please contact us: client@webgroup-limited.com

## Personal Information Collected

We collect personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when joining the ONLYBLOWJOB Site. This information includes your email address and a password when you join ONLYBLOWJOB.

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. By accessing and using our Site, you signify your consent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site or contact us for adaptation in the limit of our possibilities.

Upon request we will deliver you a report of your personal information and all datas related to you collected by us. If your personal information is incorrect or incomplete, you have the right to ask us to update it. For that purpose contact us at : client@webgroup-limited.com. You also have the right to ask us to modify the processing of your personal information. You can also ask us to delete or restrict how we use your personal information, but this right may impact your access to some of our Services

To claim one of these above mentioned rights, or just get additional informations please contact us: client@webgroup-limited.com

## Cookie Policy

When you visit or interact with our sites, services, applications, tools or messaging, we or our authorized service providers may use cookies and other similar technologies to help provide you with a better, faster, and safer experience, and for advertising and marketing purposes. When you visit our Sites, there’s certain information that’s recorded which is generally anonymous information and does not reveal your identity. If you’re logged into your account some of this information could be associated with your account. We’re talking about the following kinds of details: 

  1. Your IP address or proxy server IP address;
  2. The domain name you requested;
  3. The name of your internet service provider is sometimes captured depending on the configuration of your ISP connection;
  4. The date and time of your visit to the website;
  5. The length of your session;
  6. The pages which you have accessed;
  7. The number of times you access our site within a given month;
  8. The file URL you look at and information relating to it;
  9. The website which referred you to our Sites;
  10. The operating system which your computer uses.

To use the website without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.)

In case you do not authorise any cookie and you do not wish to use the cookie preference of your browser please contact us here to get access to our services without cookies. In case you do not agree with this, please contact us by email: client@webgroup-limited.com

## Your personal information storage

We store personal information on secure servers that are managed by us and our service providers. Personal information that we store or transmit is protected by security and access controls, including username and password authentication, two-factor authentication, and data encryption where appropriate.

## Third Party Billing Companies

The third party billing companies which collect your payment for using our services collect personal and billing information that we have access to but do not store. You acknowledge and agree that we do not have any responsibility for the collection, maintenance or safeguarding of the privacy of any such personal or billing information provided to such third party billing companies and that such responsibility is solely between you and the third party billing company. We encourage you to examine and determine your satisfaction with the policies of such third party billing companies prior to your using them.

## When and With Whom We Share Your Personal Information

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

## How We Protect the Security of Your Personal Information

We use Data Encryption in efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures.

**Communications from the Site**

  * **Special Offers and Updates**  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.
  * **Newsletter**  
Where we have your consent to do so (e.g. if you have subscribed to one of our email subscription lists or have indicated that you are interested in receiving offers or information from us), we send you marketing communications by email about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. You can ‘opt-out’ of such communications if you would prefer not to receive them in the future by using the “unsubscribe” function provided in the communication itself.

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect to our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections. 

  * **Service Announcement**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. These communications are not promotional in nature. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we may send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications.
  * **Customer Service**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email, in accordance with the users wishes.

## Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of receiving Special Offers, Updates, and Newsletters. Users who no longer wish to receive emails of this nature, may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the Unsubscribe link included in the emails or directly emailing us at : client@webgroup-limited.com

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We will occasionally modify this Privacy Policy by posting such changes on this page. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use ONLYBLOWJOB, it is suggested to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. 

Each of the changes will also be sent to you by email. 

## Outbound Links

The Sites may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave ONLYBLOWJOB they should read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

## How to Contact ONLYBLOWJOB

If you have comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us through our [support form](http://ddfsupport.com/) or via email at support@ddfsupport.com.

ONLYBLOWJOB is a site of DDF Communications, s.r.o. Krakovská 1366/25, Nové Město, 110 00 Praha 1

Only Blowjob is the Ultimate Babes Blowjob & POV site with Best 4k Porn and Full HD XXX Videos for 2019
